I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- [F54] Canadian Fur Trappers Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 54)
  Decisions: 1) 2/24/71. Vacation pay. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 9/1/71. Vacation pay. Contains correspondence. 3) 9/13/72. Refusal to pay; rates of pay; vacation pay. Contains correspondence.
- [F55] Susan Carol Furs Ltd., 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 55)
  Decisions: 1) 2/11/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 12/15/71. Successor company; welfare funds. Contains notes.
- [F56] Carillon Furs, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  Decisions: 1) 9/8/71. Contracting out. 2) 6/2/72. Discharge; improper personal conduct. Contains notes.
- [F57] Carlyle Furs, Ltd., 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  Decisions: 6/25/69. Falsification; files. Contains notes. 2) 7/2/70. Termination of business; compensation. Contains notes and exhibits. 3) 7/29/70. Refusal to pay; rates of pay.
- [F58] Celeste Furs, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  Decisions: 1) 2/21/73. Employer-union relations; Employer associations. 2) 3/27/74. Contracting out.
- [F59] Cela Furs, Inc. 3/18/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  Decision: Reduction in force. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- [F60] Cela-Helfand, Inc. 9/14/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 60)
  Decision: Supervisors and foremen; fights and altercations. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F61] Cenco Trading Corp. 8/31/72, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  Decision: Vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F62] Chambers Sherwin, Inc. 1/28/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  Decision: vacation pay.
- [F63] Chateau Creations. 9/8/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 63)
- [F64] Chattman-Fuhrman, Inc. 11/1/74, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  Decisions: Successor companies; crew size; assignment of jobs. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F65] Maroin Cherkoss, Inc. 11/26/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  Decision: Discharge; absenteeism. Contains notes.
- [F66] City Fur Co., Inc. 2/1/71., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  Decision: Termination of employment; Notice. Contains notes.
- [F67] Clay Furs, Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  Decisions: 1) 11/13/68. Rates of pay. 2) 11/20/68. Rates of pay; employer associations. Contains notes and correspondence. 3) 9/4/69. Assignment of jobs. Contains notes. 4) 12/29/69. Overtime; employee rights. Contains notes. 5) 2/6/70. Holiday pay; vacat
- [F68] Cohen & Hoch, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  Decisions: 1) 9/26/68. Removal of work from the bargaining unit; supervisors and foremen; overtime. 2) 4/15/70. Overtime. Contains notes.
- [F69] Coopchik Furs, Inc. 7/19/73 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  Decision: Quits. Contains notes.
- [F70] Corinna Furs, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  Decisions: 1) 10/14/70. Contracting out. 2) 3/5/71. Bargaining in good faith; identification of employer. Contains notes.
- [F71] Craft Furs Co., Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  Decisions: 1) 1/23/69. Union security. 2) 11/18/70. Files. 3) 11/27/70. Contracting out. Contains notes.
- [F72] Crest Furs Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  Decisions: 1) 9/14/68. Discharge; standards of production. Contains notes. 2) 7/29/69. Contracting out. 3) 2/22/73. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains exhibits. 4) 2/26/73. Rates of pay.
- [F73] Crest Novelty Corp., 1970-1973 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  Decisions: 1) 9/23/70. Welfare funds; pensions. Contains notes. 2) 7/25/73. Contracting out. Contains exhibits.
- [F74] Cristal-Schuchman & Co., Inc., 1968 (Box 36, Folder 74)
  Decision: 1) 4/22/68. Employees rights. Contains notes. 2) 9/9/68. Crew size. Contains notes.
- [F75] Cutler Fur Corp. 2/3/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 75)
- [F76] D&J Fur Co., Inc. 2/23/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 76)
  Decision: vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F77] D-K Fur Corp. 6/4/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 77)
  Decision: Removal of work from bargaining unit; supervisors and foremen. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F78] Daka Furs. 1/27/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 78)
  Decision: Holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F79] Daniel Fur Co., Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 36, Folder 79)
  Decisions: 1) 5/15/68. Contracting out. 2) 8/26/70. Holiday pay. 3) 11/24/70. Assignment of jobs. Contains notes. 4) 2/10/71. Holiday pay; Vacation pay. Contains exhibits. 6) 3/22/71. Interpretation of past arbitration award; Termination of business. Cont
- [F80] Davsons Furs, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 36, Folder 80)
  Decisions: 1) 4/1/71. Call-in. Contains notes. 2) 3/28/72. Discharge; leaves of absence. Contains notes. 3) 12/3/73. Discharge; absence. Contains notes, exhibits.
- [F81] Debutante Furs, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 36, Folder 81)
  Decisions: 1) 4/19/68. Rates of pay. Contains notes. 2) 1/22/69. Overtime. 3) 1/3/69. Contractual duties. 4) 11/24/70. Discharge; theft. Contains notes and exhibits. 5) 2/10/71. Vacation pay. 6) 3/17/71. Vacation pay. 7) 12/15/71. Reduction in force. 8) 1
- [F82] DeJour Furs, Inc. 9/20/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 82)
- [F83] Dekon Furs, Inc. 10/2/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 83)
  Decision: Rates of pay; vacation pay. Contains correspondence and exhibits.
- [F84] Demain Furs Ltd., 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 84)
  Decisions: 1) 1/14/73. Contractual duties. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 1/14/73. Removal of work from the bargaining unit, supervisors and foremen. Contains notes and correspondence. 3) 1/14/73. Holiday pay. Contains notes and correspondence. 4)
- [F85] Nicholas DeMayo Co., Inc. 10/20/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 85)
  Decision: Union security. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F86] Derman & Helfand, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 86)
  Decisions: 1) 11/21/68. Removal of work from the bargaining unit. Contains notes. 2) 1/21/68. Overtime. Contains notes. 3) 11/21/68. Employees rights. Contains notes. 4) 8/14/69. Contracting out. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F87] S&A Diamond, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 87)
  Decisions: 1) 9/30/68. Discharge; absenteeism; tardiness; improper personal practices. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 2/18/70. Vacation pay. 3) 3/30/70. Assignment of jobs. Contains notes. 4) 4/29/70. Vacation pay.
- [F88] Doumas Bros. 2/17/71, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 88)
  Decision: Vacation pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F89] I. Dover Furs, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 36, Folder 89)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/72. Discharge; quits. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits. 2) 10/23/74. Leaves of absence.
- [F90] Dutch American Fur Corp., 1971-1972 (Box 36, Folder 90)
  Decisions: 1) 4/14/71. Files. Contains notes, correspondence and agreements. 2) 5/17/71. Interpretation of past arbitration award; damages. Contains notes and correspondence. 3) 5/19/72. Crew size. Contains notes and correspondence. 4) 5/19/72. Contractin
- [F91] Egelberg & Rabach, Inc. 10/26/72, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 91)
  Decision: Recall. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F91A] Eiger & Zaretsky, Inc. 9/5/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 92)
  Decision: discharge; absence. Contains notes.
- [F92] Herbert Eisenberg. 9/27/72, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 93)
- [F93] Eldee Furs. 1/29/69, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 94)
- [F94] Furs by Eldon, Ltd. 5/12/75, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 95)
  Decision: Identification of employer. Contains notes.
- [F95] Epstein & Gross, Inc. 12/10/68, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 96)
  Decision: Overtime. Contains notes.
- [F96] Furs by Samuel T. Erdheim, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 36, Folder 97)
  Decisions: 1) 5/2/68. Overtime. 2) 1/6/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F97] Ben Eskin., 1970-1974 (Box 36, Folder 98)
  Decisions: 1) 3/25/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 10/14/70. Contracting out. 3) 2/3/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 4) 9/20/73. Assignment of jobs. Contains notes. 5) 5/1/74. Discharge; improper personal conduct; incompetence and inefficiency.
- [F98] Esserman & Peres, Inc. 2/18/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 99)
- [F99] Exelbert Fur Corp. 4/29/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 100)
- [F100] Fantasia Furs, Inc. 4/27/72, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 101)
- [F101] Feingold & Goldberg, Inc. 9/9/68, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 102)
  Decision: Crew size. Contains notes.
- [F102] Harold Feldman, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 36, Folder 103)
  Decisions: 1) 10/12/71. Identification of employer. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 12/20/72. Rates of pay. 3) 7/17/74. Rates of pay; supervisors and foremen.
- [F103] Israel Feldman Fur Corp. 3/4/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 104)
- [F104] Paul Feldman & Sons, Inc. 11/4/70, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 105)
- [F105] Philip Feldman Furs, Inc. 11/7/73, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 106)
  Decision: Discharge; absence; tardiness. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F106] Sol E. Feldman Furs, Inc., 1971 (Box 36, Folder 107)
  Decisions: 1) 10/6/71. Contracting out. 2) 10/20/71. Overtime.
- [F107] Fink & Feinberg, Inc., 1973 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Decisions: 1) 2/23/73. Contractual duties; Assignment of jobs. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 6/28/73. Contracting out. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F108] Sam Fink Furs., 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Decisions: 1) 1/24/73. Holiday pay; vacation pays. 2) 6/26/74. Vacation pay. Contains correspondence.
- [F109] Mike Forrest, Inc. 5/26/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  Decision: sick leave.
- [F110] Fourrures Sport Walt Stiel, Ltd., 1971-1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Decisions: 1) 6/2/71. Discharge; incompetency and inefficiency. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits. 2) 5/19/71. Rates of pay. Contains notes. 3) 9/7/72. Vacation pay. 4) 10/12/72. Assignment of jobs; schedules of work. Contains notes. 5) 6/7/73.
- [F111] Foxcraft Furs, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  Decisions: 1) 11/25/69. Falsification; files. Contains notes. 2) 10/14/70. Contracting out.
- [F112] Foxes Original, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  Decisions: 1) 2/24/71. Holiday pay. Contains notes. 2) 11/14/73. Vacation pay.
- [F113] Fredrica Furs, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/71. Reinstatement; Medical release. Contains notes. 2) 1/14/72. Union representative and business; overtime; welfare funds; pension funds. Contains notes.
- [F114] L.J. Freiman, Inc. 1/23/69, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  Decision: Crew size.
- [F115] Friedman &; Hirschhorn Corp. 1/28/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  Decision: holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F116] Friedman, Rosen &; Bachner, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  Decisions: 1) 11/6/68. Crew size. Contains notes. 2) 11/27/68. Discharge; tardiness. Contains notes. 3) 1/15/69. Interpretation of past arbitration award; crew size. Contains notes. 4) 2/11/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 5) 4/21/70. Removal of work from t
- [F117] Murray Furst, Inc. 7/10/69, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  Decision: Removal of work from the bargaining unit; supervisors and foremen. Contains notes.
- [F118] G.B. Furs, Inc., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  Decisions: 1) 2/4/70. Overtime. 2) 9/23/70. Union security. Contains notes.
- [F119] G.G.B. Fur Corp., 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  Decisions: 1) 6/8/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay; damages. 2) 6/17/70. Damages. Contains notes. 3) 9/14/70. Reduction in force; crew size; contractual duties. 4) 10/22/70. Reinstatement. Contains notes. 5) 5/26/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F120] Galuten Furs, Inc. 3/23/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- [F121] Paul Garvin Associates, Inc. 10/21/74, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  Decision: reinstatement; medical release. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F122] Gayle Furs, Inc. 2/12/71., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  Decision: supervisors and foremen. Contains notes, correspondence, and exhibits.
- [F123] S. Gelfand &; Son, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  Decisions: 1) 5/2/68. Overtime. 2) 6/20/73. Contracting out. 3) 5/29/74. Discharge.
- [F124] Gellert &; Kaden, Inc., 1972 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  Decisions: 1) 10/12/72. Assignment of jobs; equalization. Contains notes and exhibits. 2) 12/20/72. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains exhibits.
- [F125] Gem Fur Co., Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  Decision: 12/11/68. Identification of employer. 2) 1/27/71. holiday pay.
- [F126] George Furs. 12/16/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  Decision: Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F127] George Bros. Furs, Inc. 3/18/70., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- [F128] George P. Furs. 11/24/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  Decision: Contracting out. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F129] Gessin Furs, Inc. 2/17/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  Decision: holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F130] M. Getto &; Sons, Inc. 6/18/69, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  Decision: Union security; welfare funds; pension funds. Contains notes.
- [F131] Gi Fashion Sales, Inc., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  Decisions: 1) 2/4/70. Crew size; contracting out. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 3/27/70. Interpretation of past arbitration award. Contains notes, correspondence and awards. 3) 5/25/70. Interpretation of past arbitration award. Contains notes and
- [F132] Oliver Gintel, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  Decisions: 1) 9/13/68. Overtime; contract modifications; union representative and business. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 1/23/69. Overtime. 3) 11/5/69. Identification of employer. Contains notes. 4) 12/3/69. Holiday pay. Contains notes, correspon
- [F133] Sol Gitkind Furs, Inc. 7/29/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  Decision: Holiday pay.
- [F134] H.G. Gitters, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  Decisions: 1) 10/24/68. Overtime. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 11/12/69. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 3) 11/19/69. Back pay award. 4) 12/11/69. Holiday pay.
- [F135] Sam Glasser Fine Furs, Inc. 1/27/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- [F136] Sam Glatzer Fur Co., Inc. 12/31/69, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- [F137] Ann Glenn Furs, Inc. 8/19/68 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  Decision: rates of pay. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F138] Glickman Bros. 1/16/74, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- [F139] Glotzer-Weiner &; Keppner. 1/21/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- [F140] Robert Goldberg Furs, Inc., 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  Decisions: 1) 5/20/70. Vacation pay. 2) 4/9/75. Holiday pay. 3) 6/6/75. Layoff; inability to work. Contains notes.
- [F141] Goldenberg &; Borack, Inc. 12/12/68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  Decision: Assignment of jobs; equalization. Contains notes.
- [F142] Goldner Furs, Inc. 1/17/73, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  Decision: Leaves of absence. Contains notes, correspondence and exhibits.
- [F143] Leonard Goldstein., 1970 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  Decisions: 1) 4/22/70. Union Security. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 5/15/70. Assignment of jobs; equalization. Contains notes.
- [F144] Goldstein &; Tama Furs, Inc. 1/24/73, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- [F145] Good Bros. 1/15/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  Decision: Back pay award; holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F146] S &; M Gordon, Inc. 1/3/73, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- [F147] Grauer Furs, Inc. 10/21/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  Decision: Files.
- [F148] Green-Rothman. 5/15/68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- [F149] Greenbaum and Rapps, Inc., 1959-1970 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  Decisions: 1) 12/3/59. Holiday pay. 2) 11/27/70. Holiday pay; termination of business. Contains notes.
- [F150] Furs by William Greenburg, Inc. 5/12/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  Decision: Reporting pay. Contains notes.
- [F151A] Dan Grossman, Fur Division of Richton International Corp. 10/15/73, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- [F151B] Dan Grossman, Fur Division of Richton International Corp. 10/30/74, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  Decision: Assignment of jobs; equalization. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F152] Harry and Dann Grossman. 1/29/69, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- [F153] Grubman Bros. &; Bildner, Inc. 11/4/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  Decision: part-time employees. Contains notes.
- [F154] Gruskin &; Feldman, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  Decisions: 1) 3/12/71. Discharge; notice. Contains notes. 2) 10/30/70. Assignment of jobs; equalization. Contains notes.
- [F155] H.B.A. Furs Corp., 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  Decisions: 1) 5/29/74 Assignment of jobs; equalization. 2) 5/19/75. Assignment of jobs; equalization. Contains notes.
- [F156] H.M.B. Furs, Inc., 1974 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  Decisions: 1) 10/4/74. Termination of employment; absences. Contains notes. 2) 11/1/74. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes.
- [F157] Haas Furs., 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  Decisions: 1) 8/27/70. Termination of employment; notice. Contains notes. 2) 2/25/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F158] Irving Hans, Inc., 1968-1975 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  Decisions: 1) 5/8/68. Overtime. 2) 11/12/69. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes. 3) 1/28/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 4) 1/28/70. Vacation pay; termination of employment. Contains notes. 5) 8/11/71. Leaves of absence. Contains notes. 6) 10/2/71. Te
- [F159] Hans Bros., Inc., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  Decisions: 1) 10/31/68. Rates of pay. Contains notes. 2) 11/4/68. Supervisors and foremen. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F160] Har Lee Furs, Ltd. 9/13/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  Decision: Union security.
- [F161] Harold Furs. 4/15/75, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 56)
  Decision: Union security
- [F162] Marle Harris, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  Decisions: 1) 4/24/69. Reduction in force. Contains notes. 2) 8/7/69. Leaves of absence. Contains notes. 3) 4/29/70. Contracting out. 4) 7/25/73. Discharge; improper personal conduct. Contains notes. 5) 12/24/73. Discharge; repayment to employer. Contains
- [F163] Herman Haspel Fur Mfg. Inc. 12/20/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- [F164] Herman Haspel Fur Products, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  Decisions: 1) 4/19/69. Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes. 2) 4/19/68. Removal of work from the bargaining unit; supervisors and foremen. Contains notes.
- [F165] Irving Hausman. 6/28/68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  Decision: supervisors and foremen. Contains notes.
- [F166] Hertz &; Leitzes, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  Decisions: 1) 11/13/68. Overtime. 2) 1/23/69. Union security. 3) 7/28/69. Removal of work from the bargaining unit. Contains notes. 4) 6/2/72. Discharge; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. 5) 9/21/72. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes. 6) 10/12/
- [F167] Herz Furs, Inc. 6/26/75, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- [F168] Hoch &; Mann, Inc. 5/5/75, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  Decision: Reduction in force. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F169] Hocheiser &; Friedman Furs, Inc. 12/24/68., 1968 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  Decision: Back pay award, vacation pay.
- [F170] Hochman Bros. Corp. 12/17/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  Decision: Assignment to work outside classification. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F171] Holtzbert &; Singer Furs, Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  Decisions: 1) 5/15/68. Contracting out. 2) 1/28/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 3) 9/21/72. Vacation pay. 4) 8/22/73. Holiday pay. 5) 11/7/73. Union security.
- [F172] Horowitz Fur Co., Inc. 10/4/68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  Decision: overtime.
- [F173] House of Black Diamond, Inc., 1976 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  Decisions: 1) 5/28/75. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes. 2) 6/16/75. Discharge; strikes, slowdowns &; work stoppages. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F174] Hudes Furs. 10/14/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  Decision: Contracting out. Contains notes.
- [F175] Harry Hutt Fur Co., Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/70. Vacation pay. 2) 1/13/71. Vacation pay.
- [F176] Hymore Fur Fashions, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 71)
  Decisions: 1) 7/29/69. Contracting out. 2) 10/6/71. Contracting out.
- [F177] I &; S Fur Co., Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 37, Folder 72)
  Decisions: 1) 6/28/68. Supervisors &; foremen. Contains notes. 2) 1/29/69. Vacation pay. 3) 8/31/72. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes. 4) 11/29/73. Quits. Contains notes and exhibits.
- [F178] I.W. Furs, Inc. 9/15/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 73)
- [F180] Irwin Furs. 2/28/73, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 74)
- [F181] Jordan Furs, Inc. 10/6/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 75)
  Decisions: Contracting out.
- [F182] Jorray Furs, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 37, Folder 76)
  Decisions: 1) 2/11/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 3/4/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes. 3) 3/12/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes. 4) 1/27/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 5) 10/4/72. Vacation pay; layoffs. Contains notes. 6) 2/2
- [F183] Furs by Jules, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  Decisions: 1) 4/1/70. Overtime. Contains notes. 2) 1/27/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F184] Furs by Julio, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/69. Union security. 2) 2/3/71. Vacation pay.
- [F185] Jultak Furs, Inc. 5/5/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  Decision: employees rights; assignment of jobs. Contains notes.
- [F186] Ben Kahn Furs Corp., 1968-1972 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  Decisions: 1) 12/4/68. Overtime. 2) 5/24/72. Reduction in force. Contains notes and correspondence.
- [F187] Kahn Bros. &; Pinto Inc. 1/9/69 (Box 37, Folder 81)
- [F188] Karnes &; Fischer, Inc. 10/23/68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 82)
  Decision: Overtime.
- [F189] Philip Kantor. 1/7/73, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 83)
- [F190] Kaplan &; Dollinger, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 37, Folder 84)
  Decisions: 1) 9/30/68. Employee rights; discrimination. Contains notes. 2) 12/2/68. Back pay award; call-in; supervisors and foremen; discharge. Contains notes and correspondence. 3) 6/21/72. Vacation pay.
- [F191] Jack Kasindorf. 7/12/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 85)
- [F192] Irving C. Katz Co., Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 37, Folder 86)
  Decisions: 1) 10/22/68. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes. 2) 6/13/72. Quits. Contains notes. 3) 10/20/72. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes, and exhibits. 4) 12/20/72. Severance pay. 5) 12/20/72. Sick leave and sick pay. Contains notes and ex
- [F193] Bill Kay, Inc. 12/3/69., 1969 (Box 37, Folder 87)
- [F194] Kevan Furs Ltd. 5/8/68, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 88)
- [F195] J. &; L. Kessler, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 89)
  Decisions: 1) 11/26/69. Sick leave &; sick pay. 2) 11/10/70. Discharge, alcoholism, drinking and intoxication. 3) 12/23/71. Discharge; absences. 4) 5/3/72. Employer-union relations. 5) 5/3/72. Fringe benefits; welfare funds. 6) 5/10/72. Employer-union rel
- [F196] Kigner Bros., Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 90)
  Decisions: 1) 5/8/72. Union security; supervisors &; foremen. Contains notes and correspondence. 2) 5/1/74. Holiday pay; vacation pay.
- [F197] Kirschner &; Rosenbaum Corp., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 91)
  Decisions: 1) 5/25/71. Contract modification; incentive pay and incentive systems; call-in. 2) 5/25/71. Removal of work from the bargaining unit; supervisors &; foremen. 3) 11/1/71. Reporting pay. Contains notes.
- [F198] Kirshner, Rosenbaum &; Berger Corp. 10/11/72, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 92)
- [F199] Kisilevsky &; Weiss, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 93)
  Decisions: 1) 1/28/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 2) 2/17/71. Holiday pay.
- [F200] Kisilevsky, Zuckerman &; Schwartzman, Inc. 1/28/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 94)
- [F201] Klein Bros. &; Kimmel, Inc. 10/6/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 95)
  Decision: sick leave &; sick pay.
- [F202] Jack Kobren, Inc. 7/6/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 96)
- [F203] Kolomer Bros., Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 37, Folder 97)
  Decisions: 1) 12/4/68. Overtime. 2) 2/5/69. Vacation pay. 3) 2/11/70. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 4) 1/27/71. Holiday pay; vacation pay. 5) 4/7/71. Holiday pay. 6) 3/22/72. Holiday pay. 7) 10/26/72. Holiday pay.
- [F204] Kombi Fur Corp. 3/25/70, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 98)
- [F205] David Koster Furs, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 37, Folder 99)
  Decisions: 1) 10/4/68. Overtime. 2) 12/18/74. Back pay award; vacation pay.
- [F206] Kotuk &; Ackerman Co. 9/19/68 (Box 37, Folder 100)
  Decision: crew size. Contains notes.
- [F207] J. Kotzky &; Son. 3/18/71, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 101)
  Decision: holiday pay; vacation pay. Contains notes.
- [F208] Kozee Fur Products, Inc., 1968-1975 (Box 37, Folder 102)